Guide to the Derek Shearer papers, 1972-2005.
Shearer, Derek papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Derek Shearer papers, 1972-2005.
6753
Derek. Shearer
1 cubic ft.
Printed Materials, Publications, Reports, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Planning reports, primarily relating to Santa Monica, California.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Planning reports, primarily relating to Santa Monica, California.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Shearer, Derek.
Subjects:
City planning--California--Santa Monica.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Forms part of Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning Collections.
CONTAINER LIST
- [no author provided] City of Santa Monica General Plan Land Use and Circulation Elements 1982 - 2000. San Francisco: Hall Goodhue Haisley and Barker, 1983., November 1, 1983; Document (Box 1, Folder 1)
- [no author provided] City of Santa Monica General Plan Land Use and Circulation Elements Final Adopted. San Francisco: Hall Goodhue Haisley and Barker, 1983., October 23, 1984; Document (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Appelbaum, Richard P.; Gilderbloom, John. Housing Supply and Regulation: A Study of the Rental Housing Market. (1983) The Journal of Applied Behavioral Science, 19, 1., 1983; Journal Article (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Johnston, Robert A.; Schwartz, Seymour I.. Inclusionary Housing Programs. (1983) [journal name not provided]., c.1983; Journal Article (Box 1, Folder 3)
- [no author provided] Santa Monica Real Estate Trends - A Report on 1984, A Forecast for 1985. Santa Monica: Museli Commercial Realtors, 1984., c. 1984; Document (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Capek, Stella. Tenant Organizations and Urban Policy: Lessons from a Rent Controlled City. Georgetown, TX: Southwestern University, 1986., March 7, 1986; Research Paper (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Daykin, David S.. The Limits to Neighborhood Power: Progressive Politics and Local Control In Santa Monica. Los Angeles, 1983., July 1983; Research Paper (Box 1, Folder 3)
- [no author provided] Urban Self Management in Santa Monica - Report of Comprehensive Project 217A B. Los Angeles: UCLA School of Architecture and Urban Planning, 1980.Sections: Contect of Urban Self-Management, Decentralizing the Planning Process, Public Informationa dn Communications Services, Community Economic Development, Housing, Transportation, Scenarios for Santa Monica, Urban Design, Appendices Footnotes and Bibliography, August 1, 1980; Research Paper (Box 1, Folder 4,5,6,7)
- multiple. The Derek Shearer Archive Collection - Media Folders 1 & 2 (Received July 2005)., July 2005; Photocopies of several newspaper articles, original articles. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- [no author provided] Derek Shearer Planning Commission Folder., July 1972; Folder of original newspaper articles, community corporation pamphlets, and board of directors list. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- [no author provided] Guidebook for Home-Energy Fitness. Santa Monica: Energy Fitness Program, 1984, c. 1984; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 10)
  City publication.
- [no author provided] Santa Monica Neighborhood Census 1980., c. 1980; Document (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Census publication.
- [no author provided] Guide to Property Development. Santa Monica: Community and Economic Development Department, 1983., February 1983; Document (Box 1, Folder 10)
- [no author provided] City of Santa Monica Land Use and Circulation Elements - Final Draft 1982 - 2000., 1982 - 2000; Document (Box 1, Folder 11)
- [no author provided] Join Your Neighbors…Santa Monica: Santa Monica Recycling Program, [no date provided]., [no date provided]; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Pamphlet encouraging recycling.
- [no author provided] How to Qualify for Home Weatherization. Southern California Gas Company, 1983., c. 1983; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Pamphlet describing rebates, qualifications, and rules for home weatherization.
- [no author provided] From the Studio to the Street: Proceedings of a Forum for Public Art and Update on Santa Monica's Public Art Program. City of Santa Monica Arts Commission, c. 1985., c. 1985; Bound Document (Box 1, Folder 12)
- [no author provided] Santa Monica Pier Guidelines. 1983., c. 1983; Document (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Descriptions, diagrams, and figures for the redevelopment of piers.
- [no author provided] Cooperative Conversion Feasibility Study. Santa Monica: Community Development Block Grant Program, 1981., June 1981; Document (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Extensive study.
- [no author provided] Review of California Development Fee Policies. Los Angeles and Washington, D.C.: Hamilton, Rabinovitz, and Szanton, Inc. 1982., March 1982; Document (Box 1, Folder 14)
- [no author provided] Santa Monica Rent Control: A Guide for Tenants and Landlords. Santa Monica: Santa Monica Rent Control Board, 1981., April 1981; Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Public rule and regulations guide.
- Gilderbloom, John. Moderate Rent Control - The Experiences of U.S. Cities. San Francisco: Conference on Alternative State and Local Policies, 1980., May 1980; Report (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Public policy report.